## Zerva Shikho

Date of birth: 01/01/2001 | Nationality: Syrian | Phone number: (+963) 951335417 (Mobile) | Email address:

zervashikho@gmail.com | Website: https://zerva19.github.io/zervashikho-profitol/index.html | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/zerva-shikho-a716292a9/ Address: Damascus, Syria (Home)

## **ABOUT ME**

As a front-end magician and design enthusiast, I wield pixels and code to craft mesmerizing digital experiences that spark joy and delight. With a heart set on creating intuitive and beautiful interfaces, I immerse myself in the realm of UI/UX design. Let's sprinkle some magic on the digital world together and elevate user experiences to new heights!

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

01/09/2024 - 09/12/2024 Türkiye

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER TECHNOZLEADER** 

## (Full-Time Remotely Work)

- Experience utilizing AI tools such as Heygen, Adobe Firefly, ChatGPT 4, and other
- Establish a visual identity for company projects.
- Design company documents.
- Design social media posts and videos.
- · Assist UI designers using Figma.
- Produce videos using Renderforest

16/11/2023 – 30/12/2023 Dubai, United Arab Emirates

## **UI/UX DESIGNER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER CROMIX**

#### (Full-Time Remotely Work)

## · As a UI/UX Designer:

I responsible for creating intuitive and engaging digital experiences for our products.

Involved conducting user research, creating wireframes and prototypes, and collaborating with cross-functional teams to ensure a seamless user interface.

#### · As a Graphic Designer:

Contributed to Cromix's visual identity by designing impactful marketing materials, branding assets, and illustrations that reflected the company's vision and values.

26/10/2023 - 08/02/2024 Doha, Qatar

## **UI/UX DESIGNER** BAYAAREA QATAR

## (Full-Time Remotely Work)

- · Creating and Design BayArea Website
- Understanding user needs
- Designing the user interface (UI)
- Creating wireframes and prototypes

08/02/2022 - 07/03/2023 Amman, Jordan

#### **UI/UX DESIGNER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER SAMASOFT**

## (Full-Time Remotely Work)

- Designed intuitive and engaging user interfaces (UI) for many app like Fatortak app and rent app, focusing on providing seamless user experiences.
- Created captivating and on-brand social media posts for the company, ensuring visual consistency and audience engagement.
- Developed impactful and visually appealing brochures for the company, balancing design and information to communicate key messages effectively.
- Crafted user-friendly UI designs for various company programs, prioritizing usability and accessibility.

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

10/07/2018 - 16/06/2023 Damascus, Syria

## BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN INFORMATICS ENGINEER (SOFTWARE ENGINEERING) Syria Private University

- Completed a comprehensive five-year program focusing on Software Engineering.
- Developed a solid foundation in programming languages, software development methodologies, and system design principles.
- · Acquired expertise in database management, algorithm design, and software testing.
- Graduation Project: Attained a perfect score of 100/100 for the creation of a groundbreaking multi-insurance platform, the project introducing a fully electronic system, establishing the first of its kind in Syria.

Website https://www.spu.edu.sy/

02/02/2024 - 04/03/2024

# BUSINESS MODEL CANVAS: A TOOL FOR ENTREPRENEURS AND INNOVATORS (PROJECT-CENTERED COURSE) University System of Georgia (Via Coursera)

Learned to create business models using the Business Model Canvas ,focusing on: Customer Segments, Value Proposition, Channels, Customer Relationships, Key Resources, Key Activities, Key Partners, Revenue Streams, and Cost Structure.

Field of study Marketing and advertising

06/08/2023 - 29/10/2023

## **REACT JAVASCRIPT** New Horizons

- Learned how to build interactive user interfaces using React.
- Mastered state management with React hooks.
- Implemented component-based architecture for scalable web applications.
- Practiced using modern JavaScript syntax and ES6 features.
- · Gained experience in handling asynchronous data with promises and async/await

Field of study Software and applications development and analysis

27/04/2020 - 12/09/2020

#### **FLUTTER DEVELOPER** Ousos

- Developed mobile apps using Flutter framework.
- Knowledge and practical experience in building cross-platform mobile applications.
- Implemented responsive user interfaces with Flutter widgets.
- Managed state using Flutter's state management techniques.
- Integrated third-party packages and APIs into Flutter projects.
- Published apps to both Android and iOS platforms.

Field of study Software and applications development and analysis

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ARABIC** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production		
ENGLISH	C1	C1	B2	C1	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user